# **Wesley Agena**

(808) 226-3962 1123 N92nd St. Apt. 2, Seattle, WA 98103 wesley.agena@gmail.com wesleyagena.com

# Professional Profile

My career to date includes a strong focus on refactoring legacy backend code for large applications, making the PHP/MySQL stack my strength.

However, I also enjoy expanding my comfort zone to Frontend and DevOps through side projects, where I also experiment with the current frameworks, design patterns, and other modern technologies.

**Expert** - Technologies used on an everyday basis for 5+ years, serving millions of users per day.

PHP, MySQL, Git, HTML, Bootstrap, CSS,

Familiar - Technologies used in side projects, or on a semi-regular basis for 5+ years.

- Laravel, Rest APIs, PHPUnit, Selenium, JQuery, Javascript, VueJS, ES6, LESS
- Gulp, Vagrant (Homestead), Linux, NGINX, Apache

## **Work History**

# **April 2014 - February 2016**

Senior Software Developer, Accretive Technology Group

- Port legacy payable library to REST API used across multiple products.
- Built user + internal facing system for submission, review, storage of documents (Drivers License, Passports, etc).

## October 2011 - April 2014

Software Developer, Accretive Technology Group

 Tool allowing users to query clients based on certain spending habits, and build inmail campaigns targeting those clients.

#### **Education**

Masters in Engineering Science - Computer Science University of the Pacific - Stockton, CA June 2010 - September 2011

BS Computer Science - Networking and Security University of the Pacific - Stockton, CA

May 2005 – May 2010